

# Mohammad Wahyu Sanusi Putra

mwahyu73@gmail.com | 081294946979 | Linked in | South Jakarta

## **ABOUT ME**

As a Front-End Developer with 1-year experience, I am currently focused on studying in JavaScript but exposed in all aspects of web development, version management with git. I do programming full time because I'm a "career change". I always want to learn deeply about the basics of the language and move forward to web development with the latest technology needed for work. In addition to the Language Program, I am able to install the operating system, printer and so on.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Front-End Developer

#### PT Vizitrip Global Tour (Vizitrip.com)

April 2019 - April 2020 (a year)

- Vizitrip is an Online platform providing tour packages, Open Trips, attraction tickets and Japan Rail Pass. The most complete and cheapest.
- o I am contributing to improving the homepage, tour, hotel, payment methods on the vizitrip website with React.js both desktop and mobile web view.
- User requests for a page have been adjusted to the design given and the user is satisfied with the results.

#### **IOC HELPDESK**

#### PT Infrastruktur Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Telkominfra)

July 2015 - March 2018 (3 years)

- PT Infrastruktur Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Telkominfra) is a subsidiary company of PT Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Telkom) focus on infrastructure solution business.
- I contribute in terms of customer service where if a customer experiences a problem, we are the IOC Helpdesk at the forefront to help and resolve problems that occur in the field with the assistance of field technicians from our company.
- Customer complaints are resolved, customers are satisfied and infrastructure is back to normal.

## **AWARDS**

Frontend Development Scholarship Awardee from Facebook at OpenClassrooms

Frontend Developer Path 2019

Students at OpenCLassrooms start date January 1, 2019 - end date September 31, 2019. Europe's largest online education platform. Field of study Front-end Developer Path. Coursework included HTML, CSS, Javascript, etc.

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

Full Stack Web Course (Javascript) 2018

Student at <u>ImpactByte</u> start date July 31, 2018 - end date September 21, 2018. Coursework included Front-end Website, Back-end Website.

### **EDUCATION**

o <u>Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika</u>

Informatics Management

Associate's Degree (D3) March 2012 - November 2015 ( 3 years).

UBSI a private tertiary institution located in Jakarta, Indonesia. On March 3, 1988 Bina Sarana Informatika Computer Education Institute (LPK BSI) was established in Depok. This educational institution aims to educate skilled workers or professionals in the field of computers, to meet the needs of human resources in national development.

o STMIK Nusa Mandiri Jakarta

Information Systems

Bachelor's Degree (S1) September 2016 - November 2017 (a year).

STMIK Nusa Mandiri Jakarta is one of the favorite campuses for prospective new students at D.K.I. Jakarta. The location is on Jl. Peace No. 8 Warung Jati Barat (Wildlife) South Jakarta 12540 D.K.I. Jakarta

o <u>Impact Byte Jakarta</u>

Bootcamp Full Stack Web Development

July 2018 - September 2018 (2 months)

Impact Byte is a fast track bootcamp coding for professional coding training in Indonesia.

# **SKILLS**

HTML Git •••••

CSS Jira / Agile ••••

JavaScript Installing OS ••••

React.JS Setup Printer ••••

# **HOBBIES**

- o Playing Badminton
- Pet Lover (Cat & Bird)
- o Radio Listener

# **REFERENCES**

- o Danang Eka Alfianto from PT Vizitrip Golbal Tour 085624503065
- o Sigit Setiaji from PT Vizitrip Golbal Tour 081294388137
- Fildzah Fauziah Nur Shabrina from PT Infrastruktur Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Telkominfra) - 081282771623
- Ariz Boy Chandra from PT Infrastruktur Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Telkominfra) - 081311472721